Yeah, I'm not gonna be letting people just like abuse the show anymore. So Gotti and Joe you are banned
Really like not like
But I bet to ban you from the chat too. I mean, it's like
You're good. Oh, yeah, you did. Yeah, you did. I told you not to say it, you know, you don't have to say it. It's fine
Good, well, you know, you just think you know if you want to ever be on the path
It's like you can't control yourself. He can't control himself. You don't need to be on
Tired of like ending my shoes for some reasons, right?
Don't say nice
I mean, it's like I only have to I only only told him about it, you know a thousand times not stop saying that
He knew he was
It's not good for
The algorithm is I can't explain it anymore. It's like it's just like I know people that are shadow band because of it
Oh, this is hurt me and this makes you look ignorant. Okay. Hey Janet
Hey ending. I hate having to end streams that I think I don't like to have to continually tell people that's why I like, you know
the monetized panel because people can't behave themselves.
It's like...
Hi, babe.
Hi, Rudy.
There's Rudy.
Hey, Rudy.
I mean...
Thank you to everyone who's nice to me because it's like I get kicked on so much.
That it's like hard
But yeah, thank you for thank you for whoever is like this even if you don't like me there's respectful people
There's like people that know how to like at least have some respect
And it's like people like continually do these things saying yeah
continually making like this is terrible
Um, I don't know these jokes about you know, mother's dying and then laughing hysterically like it's some kind of funny joke
Right, it's like those aren't funny jokes
It's like and if we have people who's you know lost mothers and it's like will be hurt
And it's like why I don't understand why people are laughing at it. I hear people that I thought were like sweet people too
You know like really sweet people just like taking on this like evil
died or say, oh, they want they want people to die and people to suffer and people
I was just like what's going on in the world, right?
Like I never said anything rude. Yeah, I've never gone on anybody's panel and said the and said the n-word like that
like especially after you know
I never said that like that and then for it then keep repeating it like so
It's like basically was said like basically three times or three or four times in like two seconds, you know
a little bit overkill so if you
Horrific week. Yeah, I know I know Jan Jamie. Yeah, I know it's been really tough on you
It's like, you know, then the Michaels passed away and
You think like people passing away like in our community would be like, oh, well, maybe like
Should be like a little bit kinder or no
Anyway
Can't take I can't take the panels anymore of just like thank you
Who am I looking for are you buying me a chicken?
Hey Joe, I mean, it's like, you know, you knew you knew better
That's the problem was you knew better and I even said like you even asked can I say that can I say the n-word?
And I was like no and then you said it
Then God he starts saying and then it's like it's this
Right. Yeah, I know I don't think I ever get invited to the to the cookouts, right?
You know, I'm the only the only thing that ever anybody ever wants to cook is me and
You know, I really don't I'm not about that. I mean, it's like the show is going
Huh, I
Don't say it ever. I mean, I don't say either. I mean
But I guess it is part of some people's vocabulary, but it's like it's just not
Don't know anybody else here. No, you could probably see my face
I had to take off my headphones for a second so I could like, you know pull my hair back a little bit
You know all of a sudden I hear the n-word
The hard ER
About three times
So it's like I have to be careful who I'm gonna be on the panel now. It's like, you know
Some people don't care what happens to my show, but I care, okay?
So, well, go ahead and go ahead and use a Billy, but it's like, you know, don't use it on my panel
You know you go say it, you know
In your context, but I don't like the word I don't like I don't like any kind of like race
I don't like the racial language. I don't like
Dehumanizing language or
You know, I don't like mean
Like cruelty, I don't like it
Thank you, I
Know it's in some people's like vernacular, right? Okay, I won't go on about it, but
Here's Rudy. I don't mind up
It's like I'm but it's like I don't know
Do you guys notice that maybe what makes me such an easy target though?
It's like is there something about me that this is like
Needs to be needs to be attacked constantly
Okay, I was able to delete the stream. I was only a few minutes. It wasn't like I like it was just this is disrespect basically
Yeah, Rudy you want some catnip?
And there's a lot and there's a lot of disrespect that goes on and it's like and I notice it and it's like it's like a lot of
It's because I've been through like, you know
narcissistic abuse cycles, you know many times, you know
So many times like over and over it is a circle. It's like a you know a cat's fine Rudy's right here
He's the cat's fine. Look right here
So I know gaslighting I know
Subliminals, you know, I don't use them. I understand them because they've been used on me
You know what subliminals are guys? It's like something almost like a dog whistle kind of thing
It's like something that it's like
You know and you can tell I can just tell even if I don't know what they're talking about
I can tell that it's like it's just like stories that make no sense
like
Because I think something's funny and then they start laughing about something. That's not I don't understand
Guys you ever hear that you want be a way to go find her. Let me Joe's dick pig later for me
Oh, I don't want to see that that that uh, he's red his pink dick or red dick or what? I don't know what color it is
He's redheaded
Beata doesn't like me anymore. You just said that you know, she doesn't want to ever see me again talk to me again
She I said hi to Kate and you know, she
So she hates me now, so
I've apparently just been a terrible person and like let her be constantly
You know attacks and everything kind of I don't know
Well, I would be cooler if like, you know people could
You know just like be normal, but
Always gotta keep keep pushing past the oops. Sorry, babe
Like literally
Ah, I just say I don't do that to people and so when it's just like done to me like not even just like
I'm pat it's just done constantly. It's like there's this where's on you
Constant
Like there's like there's uh-huh and then it's like, oh, okay. Well, okay. Here's low. Here's a love bomb
Here's a love bomb. You know, I'm a cool person. We're friends then it's like
Your piece of shit. I hate you. I hope everyone you everyone you love dies. That's basically the attitude I get right
Where are they gone? Oh be I don't know beat it that she's not coming here anymore. Like she like because apparently like I
something
Horrible, I don't know
I said I did say I was in case because I saw my name and I saw my name a few times
And so I was I commented a couple times explaining
the story because they didn't have all the all the details and
And then she said hi psyche and I said hi
That was
So anyway, sorry, I'm sorry to sorry, it's a good not
happiest
Happiest trip I get very sensitive to
to disrespect sometimes.
I'm not kind of maybe just encouraged.
I don't know.
I guess it's like, it is probably my fault.
I'm like, I allow,
I teach people how to treat you and stuff like that, right?
I don't think I've been.
But I think that is,
I'm reading your comments, but what but what but I'm sorry. I'm talking. What's your comment?
And you get mad at me for telling you people think you're a locale. I wasn't being mean I liked you
But you don't care you'd like abuse. Okay. Well, whatever thing that is
Whatever, it's your problem now. Bye. I mean geez
I don't care if the people think I'm a locale, you know, it doesn't really matter to me, as long as my show's okay, like my show's doing well.
And it is.
It's doing really well, but it's constantly under attack.
Let's do what it when you gonna learn dude guy don't care. It's not his channel. Yeah, he doesn't care
So he's not coming up. He's not coming up against. I'm sick of his big little
His his jokes, you know, he was another one just pretending to be nice
Joe is used to hanging out with knuckled draggers like good times and all do not civilize people. Well, how civilize them?
I mean, I was like, I'm not saying I'm mean anybody special or anybody better or worse or anybody
Everybody's fine. It's just like how people treat me if I treated people like they treated me. They wouldn't like it. They wouldn't
They would actually probably like, you know, want to
You know do some things to me, you know, I say right. It's like that's what cool usually acts
But receiving such horrible abuse, and I would have read your comment and seen that as, but whatever.
So I'm not going to miss comments, you know. I'm kind of talking right now.
If I if I am a low cow, I am like the most beautiful fucking
I'm like the white minotaur and
You know, well, you know Poseidon gave Kimino's this white bull
And he's like but sacrifice the bull. I mean, this is like well, I like the bull so much. I'm not gonna sacrifice it
And that bull it's the white bull, so I'm a beautiful white bull, right?
Where'd I shave it?
Um, it was just getting big. I know it's kind of probably doesn't look good. I felt like I was getting a little bit shaggy
It was all gray on on tiktok. No
Kind of like it tiktok is kind of harder because it's like you see like you can see when people come in the room
Because they they are scrolling down, you know, most people are just gonna scroll or doom scrollers would be scroll through people's pages, right?
But it then it's like hard when there's like nobody that in there and it was like, you know, so I don't know I was thinking I was
not good looking enough for
The platform or whatever, but I did okay a couple of the shows I did okay, but I
Don't know it can't really compete
Also, it really is also if I smoke a cigarette they fucking start diverse. They restrict my video they fucking
You can't even blow smoke in the out anywhere, right?
Or you get restricted so it's kind of too strict. I like you too because it's not that strict with it
I've been okay at least some people get kicked off right away
Um, hi Jamie me and Slayer are in bed watching the show. Okay, good
No, it's
Feel bad, you know Michael was always Michael was always the
Pretty nice to me sometimes he was annoyed with me, you know
And he would get kicked sometimes and he'd be annoyed and he'd be like, oh, you're a cowards like you blah blah and
But then I think like one of the last things he said to me was he loved me and
You know, I kind of feel really bad, but I
You know this last time I
Yeah, you know I need to talk to him. I hope he didn't feel bad. You know
I'll keep trying I mean I did I was I had a good teacher to show the other day and
Then you know I did a lot of readings and then I was like it was I don't know if my microphone works
and today no one was talking to me in the chat at all and
That's my cat or day. It's not very good
Yeah, I would like this morning like I you know just get
Turn on the turn on the someone's stream and then it's like oh, you know, I'm a people are just like oh, you know everyone's
Oh, everyone's mad at me and not really anybody was even mad at me
I don't know who came over the show that's because I just talked to crucible gross. He was the donator. He wasn't mad at me
He was good. He was he's like, oh cool
And you know and then Chris, I don't think Christine was mad at me
I don't even think summer was mad who was mad at me like I don't understand who was the
What happened? Well, you know be to call me yelled at me like again
Like but I yelled back this time because it's like I usually I'll just sit there listen take it take it take it take it
Take I apologize apologize apologize this time. I was like well, you know what?
I don't think I did anything wrong, and it's like in you and I don't know
Why is I
Never I never talk about other people's their business. Okay, this is a this is like this is like and especially like
Me with five cats and stuff like that, you know, I do a lot of expenses. Okay, it's expensive
five cats are expensive
But so people want to or so want to need to take money out of my pocket for what reason it's like what?
anybody with
People have jobs and sometimes people are jealous of the jobs I guess but it's like people aren't usually like
Say well, how much money did you make? Well, what do you do?
Well, you just sit in an office and like sit by a computer and you know, you make money
It's like yeah, you know people make money by working because of this work when you're gonna get a real job, so like
I'm who's business is it? It is hard to please everybody, but it's like and I tried I tried
Compromising me everyone happy and I was but then I get called all these like
Disparaging thing. Oh, I'm I'm charging everybody to come on the panel. Oh, you know, it's like I'm just care about money
I'm just like you you know, I don't whatever I
Get disrespected more than anybody on the show. It's my show
I've never seen a show where the host has been disrespected so much
Well, Billy they could talk to me I could I could give them some advice. I have a marketing degree
I am focused I have focused on this as a career
I don't know if people picked up on that it's like this was like I was like I went I haven't like worked for a while
I was very excited to like do something and actually like be
Well be able to make a little profit. I could you know never have to don't have to worry too much about
You know
Ring it up. I don't know. It's been good. I don't know why people have a problem with me. It's like I know it's not
Hold on a second
Okay, guys, well, it's good that I ended the last thing so I'm just gonna message
I'm gonna be mass flagged now because and it said you're sucking it then it says
Somebody's name. I'm sucking their titty again
And it says nasty work by you psyche. What does this say keep talking about me? What I say?
Well, I said I said well she hates me too. Well, what did she just say that on the phone beta like what I said
She hates me too. Yeah
I was very hateful like a couple phone call. I just received from you yelling at me. Yeah, I know. Yeah
So anyway, whatever
But yeah, so when I'm getting
Because I have one person in my chat, you know apparent. I'm not even let it so whatever. I'm not doing anything wrong. So
Sit there and waste your time. They're gonna block your account if you mess flag me for wasting their time
What else can I take it as if I've hated is this like supposedly?
Yeah
Thank you, Yon
Thank you
You know what it's like
As for other people, you know, I know people have problems with people. I try to be cordial to everybody
It's that you know other content creators
I want to get and it's like and then every other week they're fine and then they're like calling the police on each other
They're fine again. It's like it's like it's like to what why are people are they're allowed to have a relationship and talk?
Why can't I I'm not allowed to not allowed to talk to people and I love to say hello. Someone says hello to me
Who made you say it, Joe?
Someone made you say it.
Those motherfuckers, okay.
Well, I don't know.
They did, they made you say it.
Okay, well, sorry that you're a puppet, Joe.
If you're just doing what people tell you to do.
Mm-hmm, right Billy it's it's really it's relatable right it's relatable
Okay, thank you TNC yeah, I will I will I will and I'll just keep going
Yeah, they made Joe put 30 anal beads up me and eat it out my god
Okay, this is sake beat us. I mean why you get Janet modded after all the stuff. She said about you and be that she hates you Janet hates
You sake she's a leech
Janet's absolutely fine. Oh
Like sometimes yeah when people are fighting sometimes they'll say things and you know, but
People said things about me that I get mad about I'm not supposed to be mad, right? So
Yes, it's okay. It's okay. Please do actually because I like I like to harvest that harvest that sexual energy for power
It's kidding
so anyway
Mm-hmm
And it's like it is I and I'm nice and it's like people are like oh look at what you're doing
Like I'm like like this like the worst person in the world that makes me think like what am I doing something like so my
My evil didn't I didn't call you right now. I actually you called me. I said that that wasn't you on the phone
No, that was it. You did you text message me. Hello
She didn't call me just now, but she called me this morning. Yeah, I said you called me like yeah, you call me during Kate's show
I didn't say you called me right now.
I said, I read the message where you said,
oh, nasty work, psyche.
I said, oh, Bita hates me because, yeah, you did.
Basically said you hated me.
You don't wanna talk to me over again.
You're gonna stay away from me.
It was hours ago, Bita, it was less than an hour ago, okay?
It was not hours ago, okay, it's still on.
I mean, hours ago.
I mean, it's had the exact time.
It was literally less than an hour ago.
Okay, if you do false flags, okay, so there's gonna be 4,000 flags. Okay, there's gonna be 4,000 flags, right?
Okay
I mean, geez. For what? I wouldn't know. I wouldn't know for what though.
When they go, when they go 30,000 times and look what the channels flagged on many times.
Because I have Janet on, right? Imagine exposing and talking about friends. Yeah,
imagine that, Bita. Imagine that. Imagine like having your ex-boyfriend and then you come up
and you're like, oh, well, you know, you don't need cars. You're brilliant. You're brilliant.
You know, Psyche does. Psyche's asking for money. She does it for free. She does detail reading.
Okay, I can do our hour long readings. Okay, I do short readings for a show because I don't for free or whatever
Please imagine. Oh, yeah, imagine beta. Just imagine. Talk about that. Talk about a hypocrite
Yes, your ex did you remember the guy that I forgot his name, but he
The guy that put black magic on you and stuff that you all of a sudden you had him back on your show
Okay, he said it was your ex
He dated him or something
No, she's um, she's decided to I mean and I apologize then I went into case and I said hi to Kate
I didn't present anything about be there or anything nothing nothing
All I did was say hi to Kate and I was talking about and they're saying or because they were talking about me and they're saying
Oh, you know, you choose man at psyche or she you know, he was on they just brought up what happened last night
And then I pulled my side of the story because it was being misrepresented last night
Like I was like some like scamming people right again again
She's painting me like this, you know, and here's Vita with like a hundred people in her chat
I'm sitting here with like 20 people in my chat, you know trying to you know, basically, you know
Stay on on the air constantly in her attack and it's like and then right and then she's gonna say there's something
I'm doing. I don't know if it's criticism for me. I can't say hey, I didn't like how
I get I hear the little comments you make it's like yes. Oh, yes, you were talking about Alice
But you're saying oh, I'm gonna charge you I'm charging like psyche
It's too much too much too much it's too much like people getting like so mad at me so much for like no reason and it's like gosh it's like
Why like save your anger for people that actually like are doing things. It's like I know it's shit
Okay, no, I didn't end it. I didn't I had to go. What am I smoking? I was looking some weed weed in a weed and tobacco
Yeah, I'm trying to stay here
I don't know it's like people like I remember when I first started the show and I had piranha
And I think maybe beat or somebody on the panel and I was like and then someone called piranha or something a bitch
And I was like don't call her a bitch. I just got piranha's like don't she's like she's like she's like don't defend
You don't need to defend like don't defend me like I can defend myself
I can stick up for myself, you know, and I was being told oh you're being a white knight
And I was like, okay. Well, maybe I am like just being a little bit like too
Like I should let people kind of like fight their own battles
sometimes you know that I have deleted streams I have I've ended streams I've
you know at people's requests because things have been said they didn't like
okay so it's like I will I'll definitely do that I kicked people off the show I've
banned people I've hidden people because people because they said something the
person didn't like and I say I'm trying to make people happy and then you know
See, yeah, I know you're trying to help me. Thank you HK
You should the same bagel
And then Piranha the other night came on and she was like posting these links to like butthole
I mean she said it she said she wasn't but I someone send me the photo
She's like this is what it links to and it was a picture of a butthole a woman's butthole or something important and stuff and
I don't know why she would do that like
She was a mod to I
mean
I do remember that Piranha is into that furry stuff
and my Discord once had a lot of furry porn on it.
Yeah, not anymore.
Anyway, I'm sorry guys.
Okay, so let's see this true crime deck.
Spunky got me.
Let's do it. Let's do a true crime for the chat. So let's see. This might be like something that
You can relate to look these are gonna be some kind of symbols or for his or sick of
These are really I like these cut the feel of these cars. Oh shit. Is this just flopped over over wall?
Maybe we hit it we all do hit wall sometimes maybe walls are meant to protect right but they can also be climbed
You can see this one you can climb over that, right?
So there's options, even if you hear a wall,
look for like some, I look, hopefully it'll look okay.
Okay, yeah, I hope it's, I would love it
to be misunderstanding, oh, this is, by the way,
this is 33, that's the number, it says wall.
But look, there's a vine on the wall.
Maybe used by burglars. Maybe maybe could be used as an escape or if you hit it
So we all hit we all hit these walls once in a while and we'll feel like there's no way out
like look
There is way out. There's
You always
climb right?
What else we got I
Must be going
Core on Monday
Yes, we can climb we can
Let's see how we have concrete
Okay, concrete is interesting, you know, there's even something called red concrete
I think has to do with the mafia or they would like to go sometimes there's bodies in this concrete
But the concrete look it covers over things is like, you know, it just basically
Imagine all the ground under this concrete that that ground is like, you know
No longer gonna be good. Maybe a flower will come out of the one of the cracks of it or something like that, right?
Okay, Irby, what'd you say Irby? I must be going going to court on Monday. Yeah
Okay
I had I don't have the link up I pulled the concrete. Okay, so what does a concrete remind you of?
concrete a
Con has the word con right in there. C-o-n
And then Crete, where is Crete?
Crete is an island in Greece
where the King Minos was from, right?
And Crete may have been a con.
It may have been a con.
I don't know if a lot of this stuff
that we know about it, it's true,
but we'll see, maybe, oh, maybe we will.
Or maybe not meant to be known.
Okay, concrete.
Something covered up, something's been covered up.
Unbreakable? What's this one? Ooh, a coin.
Maybe there's some money under that cog for you or something.
What else is a coin? A coin is like, you know, reasons for a lot of
negativity in the world. It goes over money, right? Money is good and nice to have, but because
Different people have different capacities for earning it and
Things like that it can be it conflicts over it. Let's do a couple more
The dog tag
Military something that's a military a military person
You might have a military person in your life where you might have this a dog tag a dog tag is sometimes all that's all that's left of these people
An identifier
Okay, a tag is also kind of identifier
Nowadays we don't know for being monitored 24-7 with you know air tags, right? Thank you low-key
Okay, you have
Kate can you if that's Kate can you please just cam up just like backstage so I can just verify
100%
Or not they left so it doesn't form bombers. So
Okay
So one more card
I'm sure Logan Paul has that mass flagging campaigns as well, right? Okay, finally we have the drawer
There may be something in a drawer that will be she's gonna do emergency live. Okay?
Go ahead and I'm sure I'm sure we'll be all about you know, like how what a terrible person I am and all this kind of stuff
But she asked me not to really talk about her and I'm gonna respect her and not not talk about her anymore
But you know, she'll go do that. She'll go do the same thing to me, you know
It's like she doesn't want she wants to have the last word and like not be able to say anything and then just me like
Be worried and shit like that
It's too emotionally draining right now on me
Have enough going on I've enough people
Right the road means we got a stuff her oh come on no
Let's let's do some Van Gogh cards
Yeah, I mean it's like and it's gonna be a hate that says there's gonna be and I do have people that hate me and the people
That aren't mad about you know or that I would don't let them on the show because but you know what if I don't
If I don't right then I
Don't know people yeah
Okay, so we know it and there's a fake beta. Okay, you stop them ally. Can you just stop trying to form bomb me, please?
I bet so I'm not even gonna bring people up to slives. I'm not gonna bring people up
You please stop it. I
Mean what you're trying to impress beta now because you think she's mad at me or the Venus like what it is for you pathetic
I'm doing my best. I'm doing my best
I'll open up for ghosts for ghosts for sure ghost gets ghost kids to come on
But I've been to attempted form bombs. Okay, King of Swords
This is like, you know, getting in your king energy and like, you know, being able to state your truth being able to cut
Cut off things that aren't serving you and okay
You know, but is
Yeah, he's got these you know the cutoff game going on because he's been hurt enough. Okay, and that's true enough people lying and
Okay
Yo
Hi
I sounds like you're having a hard time, bro
Yeah, this is kind of rough
Yeah, go ahead. Sorry. No, it's just like, you know, I had it
Okay, I was just gonna say sorry to interrupt you I was just gonna say we should open it up and I was about to open it up
But when I say maybe maybe open up to people that we know, you know, I'm saying yeah, yeah
Yeah, no new people
Unless there's somebody that knows that they can vouch for them. That's fine. But yeah
I mean, I can put up the thing and everything but it's like I do have a math blogging campaign going on right now
So I really can't have any bad language
By the way, psyche on some real shit you owe me some you don't owe me nothing
But you owe me a little bit because I paid a lot of money though
Take people off which I don't know. I'm not saying listen. I don't disagree. You didn't you didn't do it. That's fine. I agree
But I did pay well seventy five dollars to get three people. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but you know, I want to take
sponsor another panel if you don't mind. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah, absolutely fine. Absolutely fine
And I just want to make sure everyone knows it's like it was like, you know, you and I are good you and I and it's like you you
Like we're brothers. We argued the brothers fight. Yeah, brothers fight. Sometimes even this fight. We're so gonna be brothers. Yeah
I really like that like out of all the people like you know
I've had like a lot of like slander and stuff going on lately and it's like you're like I don't slander
I'll slander you to your face
Because I want you to fight me, but I won't go to another panel in this respect
Well, people have something to say I wish they would just say that to my face
Even if it's like a slanderers thing like I'd rather
Slander than like these people dancing around so like or just like we see you have a chance to defend yourself
You know I'm saying insinuity. Yeah
I've been defensible with these I can't I have no idea what it is
So I can't defend it and it's like if I if I do defend
Like then people that then I remember one time it's like yeah
I was on a panel and they were talking about you of all of you of all people and they were saying something
I remember like you or you were guilty of it
I forget what they were saying and I literally argued it because I knew they weren't gonna have evidence
I knew they didn't know what the fuck they were talking about
Right
for you
Right, and it's like I really would like and it's like especially it's even been friends that did it
I think I can even like, you know
People that I say friends parentheses
People that I really like will that's big off backstage. Okay. I know what that is. That's Casey
I mean, it's like, you know, if you really want to talk to case you can like
The case he came on this morning and was like talking about like, oh, you know what I haven't talked to page for like like like a week
I think I saw her yesterday. Well, she was a beat is this morning with
But I didn't see her on the she didn't join
Yeah, I mean, it's like I don't think Paige likes me very much anymore. Like she
She seems to have some kind of problem with me. She's always being now and now and now she's being very like
It seems like I'm kind of mean. It's just kind of mean. I don't know. I don't know what I did
I don't know what I don't I don't know, but I would have paid for a page of you on here. I'll be honest
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like it's fine. I mean, it's like but uh, it seems like
People are just people are saying like weird things like when I went spunky the other day what she was saying
Oh, we were talking. It's like someone mentioned something about SUICI DE and she's like well
I look at some patients or some people sometimes and I'm like why don't you do it like and it's like that's not something
So she's looking at unalive people and she said why don't you just do it?
Yeah
She said she thought that in her mind and I was like
Well, and I don't know but maybe I don't even think is she meant it
I think it was just like kind of like something to make me she's trying to make an argument like hey
And then I put I put the G you went in your hand and then like you know like like we really want to do it
Then do it, but if you really want to do it. I don't understand the argument
I'm not trying to make an excuse for actually
Well, that's what I'm gonna make an excuse for at all
Because and then you know even that God God today was like I'm talking about driving people to S. U. I see ID
And it's like I think some of the people are trying to do that
They are trying to drive to drive people because it's like they don't break to us
I would love to have a conversation. They're in the chat by the way. I'd love that
Station as long as they don't break to us. I'd love to have it. Okay, though. They're welcome to come up here
They're welcome to come up here and have a chat, but it's like yeah
And it's like I just like I'm just saying I'm not
I'm uh, I pick up on things like I'm sensitive to energy, especially the negative energy and I feel the negative energy and maybe there's a
You know, they do feel like they have some some reason for it, but it just seems to me like it's like I
Have to agree, but I don't know the backstory. I don't know why they said that so I can't agree or disagree
But I can write if I take it if I think of it face value
face value
Nothing else considerate face value. No, you shouldn't on the light itself brother. You're not alone. We're all here
But there's some kind of argument behind it, you know, let's run it. You know what I'm saying there
There was a guy in high school and he had a girl he had this girlfriend right in the high school
This is the most assumed that you are chomo and you you can I say that word?
Let's assume that you're fine. Yeah, fine. You you got about 33 victims. Yeah, you know what fucking I'll go ahead and make
Darnit you should on the live yourself at that point. I mean, I mean one victim is too many like
Even one big
Even what even one one one victim is too many but there's things called victimless crimes too or it's like
you know people like uh it's like you know if you will go to if you go to like ghosty terminator two
and there's murderers on the in the movie and people are being shot and and blown apart it's
like does that make you a murderer and so i mean it's like it's like these are kind of like
logical it's like people are like terminator two i'd have to make argument it would you you might
uh better or maybe like war movies you know like if you go there is are you a murderer i mean yeah
Even if they're trying to attack your country you still killed them
Well, I'm feeling like it's even like even like people are people are being nicer to
You know people that have actually have victims and things like that
Then they are to me who's like not hurting anybody and so I just don't understand
It's like I don't know you're
So this is only yeah in YouTube does as it does. There's a block button, you know
And it's like and so people can block people and it's like but and I the problem is it's like
Yeah, if they were just like straight up like oh if this is this is this and telling me like they're from their truth
At least I respect that as like okay. Well, that's
It's our truth, but this is like this is like mind games kind of more or it's like they're like
They smile in your face a whole time. They want to take your place
Hold on. Yeah. Yeah, I blocked several, I mean, I can't, I mean, it's like, you know, people
are blocked at docs and stuff in my chat, but I can't really block people that are not
blocked in the chat because I have to see what people are saying or else they could be saying
terrible things in the chat and I would not be able to block them. Okay, so this is this person,
Who's Marcelle
You buy you buy it put him in the back
Is it ran is it ran? I think it's random guy hold on. I am a rid of him
He's on your left. Hello nigger nigger
Fucking oh my god, that's why I said I want